/* Creating an Array containing all the questions and answers in the boolean format */
const quiz = [
    {   
        numb: 1,
        question: "What year was Leeds United founded?",
        answer: "1919",
        options: [
            "1920",
            "1917", 
            "1919", 
            "1918" 
          ]
  },
  {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Who is the all-time leading goalscorer for Leeds United?",
        answer: "Peter Lorimer",
        options: [
            "Peter Lorimer", 
            "John Charles", 
            "Tom Jennings", 
            "Allan Clarke"
          ]
  },
  {     
        numb: 3,
        question: "Who was the latest Swedish player that played for Leeds United?",
        answer: "Pontus Jansson",
        options: [
            "Rasmus Kristensen",
            "Pontus Jansson", 
            "Tomas Brolin", 
            "Brendan Aaronson"
          ]
  },
  {
        numb: 4,
        question: "During the 19/20 season Leeds won the Championship but what were our total points?",
        answer: "93",
        options: [
            "93", 
            "92", 
            "91", 
            "90"
          ]
  },
  {
        numb: 5,
        question: "In the first season back in the Premier League with Bielsa, what rank did we end up at?",
        answer: "9",
        options: [  
            "12",
            "10",
            "9",
            "11"
          ]
  },
  {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Who was the co-owner with Andrea Radrizzani before he bought the remaining 50%?",
        answer: "Massimo Cellino",
        options: [  
            "Mariano Chellini",
            "Matteo Claudio",
            "Maurizio Costa",
            "Massimo Cellino"
          ]
  },
  {
        numb: 7,
        question: "What is a nickname for Leeds United?",
        answer: "The Peacocks",
        options: [  
            "The Marchers",
            "The Peacocks",
            "The Cockatoos",
            "The Doves"
      ]
  },
  {
        numb: 8,
        question: "What is the record attendance at Elland Road in 1967?",
        answer: "57,892",
        options: [  
        "57,892",
        "55,625",
        "52,992",
        "56,122"
          ]
  },
  {
        numb: 9,
        question: "How many members does Leeds United Supporters Club of Scandinavia have?",
        answer: "5000+",
        options: [
            "4000+",
            "2500+",
            "5000+",
            "1500+"
          ]
  },
  {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Who is the most expensive player we have bought?",
        answer: "Georgino Rutter",
        options: [
            "Raphina",
            "Georgino Rutter",
            "Brendan Aaronson",
            "Rodrigo Moreno"
          ]
  },
  {
        numb: 11,
        question: "What team did we lose to in the 2000/2001 Champions League semi-final?",
        answer: "Valencia",
        options: [
            "Lazio",
            "Real Madrid",
            "Valencia",
            "Deportivo La Coruña"
          ]
  },
  {
        numb: 12,
        question: "What is the official fee we got when we sold Raphina to Barcelona (in pounds)?",
        answer: "£50,000,000",
        options: [
            "£60,000,000",
            "£58,000,000",
            "£50,000,000",
            "£55,000,000"
          ]
  },
  {
        numb: 13,
        question: "How many Leeds players have been inducted into the English Football Hall of Fame?",
        answer: "11",
        options: [
            "11",
            "8",
            "10",
            "12"
          ]
  },
  {
        numb: 14,
        question: "During the 1960s what team inspired Revie to change our colors?",
        answer: "Real Madrid",
        options: [
            "Juventus",
            "Lyon",
            "Schalke 04",
            "Real Madrid"
          ]
  },
  {
        numb: 15,
        question: "What team did we beat in the FA Cup final in 1972?",
        answer: "Arsenal",
        options: [
            "Tottenham",
            "Liverpool",
            "Arsenal",
            "Derby"
          ]
  },
  {
        numb: 16,
        question: "How many goals did Bamford score during the 20/21 Premier League season?",
        answer: "17",
        options: [
        "18",
        "15",
        "16",
        "17"
          ]
  },
  {
        numb: 17,
        question: "What team did Marcelo Bielsa coach before Leeds United?",
        answer: "Lille",
        options: [
            "Lazio",
            "Lille",
            "Marseille",
            "Athletic Bilbao"
          ]
  },
  {
        numb: 18,
        question: "What position had former Leeds coach David O'Leary as a player?",
        answer: "Centre back",
        options: [
            "Right back",
            "Midfielder",
            "Centre back",
            "Left back"
          ]
  },
  {
        numb: 19,
        question: "In 2022 The Old Peacock Pub changed its name temporarily to what?",
        answer: "The Bielsa",
        options: [
            "The Dallas",
            "The Bamford",
            "Marching On",
            "The Bielsa"
          ]
  },
  {
        numb: 20,
        question: "Which shirt manufacturer did we have before Adidas took over in 2020?",
        answer: "Kappa",
        options: [
            "Diadora",
            "Admiral",
            "Macron",
            "Kappa"
          ]
  }];
